





Summary

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Work Authorization

Solution engineering professional leading Global IT Delivery strategy for APAC & Americas regulatory reporting domain Expert in re-engineering & design of the legacy business processes to cloud, microservices & user experience maximizations

High Stakeholder Management, Change Driver and prioritize to deliver strategic requirements with value additions Led different phases of IT projects, 20+ years technical solutions on different technical frameworks and methodologies Core deep drive abilities to find the root cause (RCA) of high severity incidents and implement short / long term plans

Work Experience

- Credit Lyonnais as Global IT Delivery Lead APAC & Americas Jul 2016 to Till Date
- A B2C Products Development Startup as Co Founder Jul 2014 to Jun 2016
- Singapore Exchange as AVP Feb 2001 to Jun 2014

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Kakatiya University in 1998

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version Last Used | Experience |
|---------------------|-------------------|-----------------------|
| Delivery Management | | 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| PROGRAM MANAGEMENT | | 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| J2EE | | 10 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld IT Service Delivery management

7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Countries: India

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.